* Subjects

* More

Your free trial awaits!
-----------------------

We're excited to get to know you! Let's start with some basic information.

Thank you! Your submission has been received!

Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.

School Name
-----------

Nice to meet you ! What school do you teach at?

Thank you! Your submission has been received!

Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.

School Location
---------------

Let's find out where   is located!

CountryUnited KingdomUnited StatesAndorraAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBolivia, Plurinational State ofBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongoCongo, Democratic Republic of theCook IslandsCosta RicaCote d'IvoireCroatiaCubaCuracaoCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatiniEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island and McDonald IslandsHoly SeeHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIran, Islamic Republic ofIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea, Democratic People's Republic ofKorea, Republic ofKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyan Arab JamahiriyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacaoNorth MacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldova, Republic ofMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian Territory, OccupiedPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunionRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaint BarthelemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Martin (French part)Saint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwedenSwitzerlandSyrian Arab RepublicTaiwanTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUnited States Minor Outlying IslandsUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaViet NamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabwe

Thank you! Your submission has been received!

Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.

Which subjects are you interested in?
-------------------------------------

Choose one or more options[](https://thisisschool-fishfinger.webflow.io/utils/popup#)

 Geography  Languages  Science  Mandarin

 French  Spanish  German  Italian  English US

 Chemistry  Physics  Biology  Combined

Thank you! Your submission has been received!

Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.

Review and Submit
-----------------

Great, let's review the information you've provided.

Firstname:  

Lastname:  

Email:  

School Name:  

Subjects: 

Country:  

Postcode:  

Do you have a referral code?

Thank you! Your submission has been received!

Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.

Thank you!
----------

We can't wait to have you on board! Our friendly team will be in touch with you shortly.

Privacy Policy
==============

Who are we?
-----------

‍

We (**“This Is School Ltd”, “TIS”** and/or **“us”** or **“we”**) ) are an EdTech company who provide online services (the “Services”) to clients who are schools and other educational establishments (“School” or “you”) to help them teach across the curriculum. This is School is a trading name of This Is Language Limited, a company registered in England and Wales whose registered office is at  6-7 Citibase - New Barclay House, 234 Botley Road, Oxford, OX2 0HP, United Kingdom with company number 07792177 .

‍

What are our legal documents?
-----------------------------

‍

[**Terms and Conditions**](https://www.thisisschool.com/terms) – For all of our School clients. These contain the legal terms and conditions on which we provide our Services to the Schools.

‍

‍**GDPR Compliance Statement** – For all of our School clients based in the EEA. It explains how we process the Personal Data that you hold within the School that you share with us.

‍

[‍**Usage Policy**](https://www.thisisschool.com/usage) – For all of our users of our Services and visitors to our website. It explains what standards we expect of you when you use our website, such as the copyright to our videos.

‍

‍[**Privacy Policy**](#) – For everyone who visits our site. It explains how we control and protect your Personal Data.

‍

You are currently reading our **Privacy Policy**…

‍

Who should read this Privacy Policy?
------------------------------------

‍

This Privacy Policy should be read by everyone who visits our site. It explains how we control and protect your Personal Data.

Privacy Policy
--------------

‍

### Introduction

###   

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your Personal Data. When you visit our website, or fill in our online trial-request form, or email us enquiring about our services, or come over and say hello during a conference, or call us to tell us that you’ve just heard something wonderful about us from another school, we (as a Data Controller) acquire basic identification data about you and we need to protect it. We are not a Controller of student data.

‍

### our Data Protection Managers

‍

TIS has appointed two Data Protection Managers who will deal with all your requests and enquiries concerning TIS's uses of your Personal Data and endeavour to make sure that all Personal Data is processed in compliance with this Policy and with the GDPR.

‍

Requests and enquiries should be sent to the Data Protection Managers at [\[email protected\]](https://www.thisisschool.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

‍

A note on EU and US data protection laws

‍

We refer to “Personal Data” in line with European and UK data privacy law (the GDPR). For our US clients the way we collect, process and disclose “Personal Data” is the exactly the same as how we collect, process and disclose “Personal Information” in line with the Children’s Online Privacy and Protection Act (COPPA) applicable in the USA and other US privacy laws.

‍

### 1\. IMPORTANT INFORMATION AND WHO WE ARE

‍

It is important that you read this privacy notice together with any other privacy notice or fair processing notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing Personal Data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. This privacy notice supplements the other notices and is not intended to override them.

‍

**Controller**

TIS is the controller and responsible for your Personal Data. TIS is the controller and responsible for the Personal Data collected from anyone who visits our site but who is not a client.

‍

**Third-party links**

This website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy notice of every website you visit.

‍

‍

### 2\. THE DATA WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU

‍

Personal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data).

‍

We may collect, use, store and transfer different kinds of Personal Data about you which we have grouped together as follows:

‍

* **Identity Data** includes first name, last name, username or similar identifier, title and email address.
* **Technical Data** includes internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this website.
* **Usage Data** includes information about how you use our website, products and services.
* **Marketing and Communications Data** includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and your communication preferences.

‍

We also collect, use and share **Aggregated Data** such as statistical or demographic data for any purpose. Aggregated Data may be derived from your Personal Data but is not considered Personal Data in law as this data does **not** directly or indirectly reveal your identity. For example, we may aggregate your Usage Data to calculate the percentage of users accessing a specific website feature. However, if we combine or connect Aggregated Data with your Personal Data so that it can directly or indirectly identify you, we treat the combined data as Personal Data which will be used in accordance with this privacy notice.

‍

We do not collect any **Special Categories of Personal Data** about you (this includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data). Nor do we collect any information about criminal convictions and offences.

‍

‍

### 3\. HOW IS YOUR PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED?

‍

We use different methods to collect data from and about you including through:

‍

* **Direct interactions.** You may give us your Identity Data by filling in forms (such as trial request forms) either online or in person or by corresponding with us by post, phone, email or otherwise.
* **Automated technologies or interactions.** As you interact with our website, we may automatically collect Technical Data about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns. We collect this Personal Data by using cookies, server logs and other similar technologies.

‍

‍

### 4\. HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA  
**‍**

We will only use your Personal Data when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your Personal Data in the following circumstances:

‍

* Where we need to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into for the provision of the Services.
* Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests
* Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.

‍

Generally we do not rely on consent as a legal basis for processing your Personal Data.

‍

Purposes for which we will use your personal data

‍

We have set out below, in a table format, a description of all the ways we plan to use your Personal Data, and which of the legal bases we rely on to do so. We have also identified what our legitimate interests are where appropriate.

‍

Note that we may process your Personal Data for more than one lawful ground depending on the specific purpose for which we are using your data. Please contact us if you need details about the specific legal ground we are relying on to process your Personal Data where more than one ground has been set out in the table below.

‍

| Purpose/Activity | Type of data | Lawful basis for processing including basis of legitimate interest |
| --- | --- | --- |
| To register you as a user or potential user of our Services | (a) Identity | Necessary for our legitimate interests |
| To process and deliver your order including: (a) Manage payments, fees and charges (b) Collect and recover money owed to us | a) Identity (b) Contact (c) Financial (d) Transaction (e) Marketing and Communications | (a) Performance of a contract with you (b) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to recover debts due to us) |
| To manage our relationship with you which will include: (a) Notifying you about changes to our terms or privacy policy (b) Asking you to leave a review or take a survey | (a) Identity (b) Marketing and Communications | (a) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation (b) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated and to study how customers use our products/services) |
| To enable you to participate in a prize draw, competition or complete a survey | a) Identity (b) Contact (c) Profile (d) Usage (e) Marketing and Communications | (a) Performance of a contract with you (b) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them and grow our business) |
| To administer and protect our business and this website (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data) | (a) Identity (b) Technical | (a) Necessary for our legitimate interests (for running our business, provision of administration and IT services, network security, to prevent fraud and in the context of a business reorganisation or group restructuring exercise) (b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation |
| To deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we send to you | (a) Identity (b) Contact (c) Profile (d) Usage (e) Marketing and Communications (f) Technical | Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, to grow our business and to inform our marketing strategy) |
| To use data analytics to improve our website, products/services, marketing, customer relationships and experiences | (a) Technical (b) Usage | Necessary for our legitimate interests (to define types of customers for our products and services, to keep our website updated and relevant, to develop our business and to inform our marketing strategy) |
| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to develop our products/services and grow our business) To make suggestions and recommendations to you about products and services that may be of interest to you | (a) Identity (b) Contact (c) Technical (d) Usage (e) Profile (f) Marketing and Communications Necessary for our legitimate interests (to develop our products/services and grow our business) (a) Identity (b) Contact (c) Technical (d) Usage (e) Profile (f) Marketing and Communications | Necessary for our legitimate interests (to develop our products/services and grow our business) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to develop our products/services and grow our business) |

Marketing

You can ask us to stop sending you marketing messages at any time by following the opt-out links on any marketing message sent to you or by contacting us at any time.

‍

Cookies

You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when websites set or access cookies. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this website may become inaccessible or not function properly.

‍

Change of purpose

We will only use your Personal Data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If you wish to get an explanation as to how the processing for the new purpose is compatible with the original purpose, please contact us.

‍

If we need to use your Personal Data for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and we will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so.

‍

Please note that we may process your Personal Data without your knowledge or consent, in compliance with the above rules, where this is required or permitted by law.

‍

‍
-

### **5.** **DISCLOSURES OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

‍

We may have to share your Personal Data with the parties set out below for the purposes set out in the table in paragraph 4 above.

‍

* Professional cloud services and technology providers such as hosting providers, CRM providers and other professional cloud services which allow us to provide our Services to you.
* Third parties to whom we may choose to sell, transfer, or merge parts of our business or our assets. Alternatively, we may seek to acquire other businesses or merge with them. If a change happens to our business, then the new owners may use your Personal Data in the same way as set out in this privacy notice.

‍

We require all third parties to respect the security of your Personal Data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third-party service providers to use your Personal Data for their own purposes and only permit them to process your Personal Data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.

‍

‍

### 6\. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS

‍

Some of our external third party professional cloud services are based outside the European Economic Area (EEA) so their processing of your Personal Data will involve a transfer of data outside the EEA. Whenever we transfer your Personal Data out of the EEA, we ensure a similar degree of protection is afforded to it by ensuring at least one of the following safeguards is implemented:

‍

* We will only transfer your Personal Data to countries that have been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection for Personal Data by the European Commission.
* Where we use certain service providers, we may use specific contracts approved by the European Commission which give Personal Data the same protection it has in Europe.
* Where we use providers based in the US, we may transfer data to them if they are part of the Privacy Shield which requires them to provide similar protection to Personal Data shared between the Europe and the US.
* Please contact us if you want further information on the specific mechanism used by us when transferring your Personal Data out of the EEA.

‍

‍

### 7\. DATA SECURITY

‍

We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your Personal Data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your Personal Data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process your Personal Data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.

‍

We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected Personal Data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.

‍

‍

### 8\. DATA RETENTION

‍

How long will you hold my Personal Data for?

‍

We will only retain your Personal Data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

‍

To determine the appropriate retention period for Personal Data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the Personal Data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your Personal Data, the purposes for which we process your Personal Data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

‍

By law we have to keep basic information about our customers for six years after they cease being customers. In some circumstances you can ask us to delete your data and please contact us if you would like further information.

‍

In some circumstances we may anonymise your Personal Data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.

‍

### 9\. YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS

‍

Under certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your Personal Data.

‍

You have the right to:

‍

**Request access** to your Personal Data (commonly known as a “data subject access request”). This enables you to receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.

‍

**Request correction** of the Personal Data that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate data we hold about you corrected, though we may need to verify the accuracy of the new data you provide to us.

‍

**Request erasure** of your Personal Data. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove Personal Data where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your Personal Data where you have successfully exercised your right to object to processing (see below), where we may have processed your information unlawfully or where we are required to erase your Personal Data to comply with local law. Note, however, that we may not always be able to comply with your request of erasure for specific legal reasons which will be notified to you, if applicable, at the time of your request.

‍

**Object to processing** of your Personal Data where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground as you feel it impacts on your fundamental rights and freedoms. You also have the right to object where we are processing your Personal Data for direct marketing purposes. In some cases, we may demonstrate that we have compelling legitimate grounds to process your information which override your rights and freedoms.

‍

**Request restriction of processing** of your Personal Data. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of your Personal Data in the following scenarios: (a) if you want us to establish the data’s accuracy; (b) where our use of the data is unlawful but you do not want us to erase it; (c) where you need us to hold the data even if we no longer require it as you need it to establish, exercise or defend legal claims; or (d) you have objected to our use of your data but we need to verify whether we have overriding legitimate grounds to use it.

‍

**Request the transfer** of your Personal Data to you or to a third party. We will provide to you, or a third party you have chosen, your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. Note that this right only applies to automated information which you initially provided consent for us to use or where we used the information to perform a contract with you.

‍

**Withdraw consent at any time** where we are relying on consent to process your Personal Data. However, this will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out before you withdraw your consent. If you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide certain products or services to you. We will advise you if this is the case at the time you withdraw your consent.

‍

If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, please contact us.

‍

No fee usually required

You will not have to pay a fee to access your Personal Data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.

‍

What we may need to know from you

We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your Personal Data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that Personal Data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response.

‍

Time limit to respond

We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated.

‍

‍

### 10\. GLOSSARY

‍

Lawful basis

‍

**Legitimate Interest** means the interest of our business in conducting and managing our business to enable us to give you the best service/product and the best and most secure experience. We make sure we consider and balance any potential impact on you (both positive and negative) and your rights before we process your Personal Data for our legitimate interests. We do not use your Personal Data for activities where our interests are overridden by the impact on you (unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law). You can obtain further information about how we assess our legitimate interests against any potential impact on you in respect of specific activities by contacting us.

**‍**

**Performance of Contract** means processing your data where it is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party or to take steps at your request before entering into such a contract.

**‍**

**Comply with a legal or regulatory obligation** means processing your Personal Data where it is necessary for compliance with a legal or regulatory obligation that we are subject to.

‍

* 2023 This is School
